Alright y'all, so a lot of people, you
know, have the information, they ready,
they heard the names, they heard the
stocks, but then now it's like, where do
you get them from? And that's a big
question that I'm going to break down
right now to help you guys at least get
access to these stocks and these tokens
and coins, right? It's not your typical
banking app, it's not your typical, you
know, you just buy it online with a credit
card, right? You have to get brokerage
accounts and you have to have, you know,
funds allocated towards these trades. So
here right now is six, basically, you
know, brokerage accounts that you can get
right now for free, download them in the
app store, sign up online. And this is
your first step to, you know, being able
to buy these things, right? Some of you
may even have access already through your
bank or your job, right? So, you know,
some of this may seem familiar, but to
those that don't, to those that, you know,
always wonder where, how, you know, you
want to definitely watch this part so you
can figure out which platform works best
for you and which one you're more
comfortable with. Alright, so we're going
to start with Fidelity. That's number one
and that's the one I use personally. So I
have my funds allocated into Fidelity
account. I have my watch list, which
again, I will show you at the end of this
video so you guys can have a, you know,
watch list for yourself if you are, you
know, having trouble finding those right
stocks, right? Fidelity, they cover
stocks, ETFs, they cover Bitcoin, they
cover, you know, direct crypto, you know,
now. So if you are signing up for that,
check that out, check the fees. I like it
personally because, you know, my bank, you
know, is able to transfer funds to it. So
that's one. And then two, it's a pretty
easy setup, you know, I don't do too much
with this. So I'm not needing a lot. I
needed to access these, these companies
and place my trades. And that's it.
Charles Schwab. That's another one. The
same thing, stocks, ETFs, they have
Bitcoin as well. They have a wallet that you
can hold your crypto in. Robinhood.
Robinhood is pretty much like a more hip,
more young, think of Cash App, but it's
for Robinhood and have a lot of other
features that you may, you know, enjoy as
a crypto user. All right. Not so much
other stocks, but the crypto is where
they're moving their rails too. So they're
focused on a crypto blockchain. And they
just released a wallet as well. So if
you're into the hip, you know, the new
things, fresh, exciting, definitely check
out Robinhood. Webull. Webull is an old
one. You know, everybody knows Webull.
Their interface and stuff is not the
favorite of mine because it's just so dull
and definitely just straightforward. And,
you know, that's not what I wanted to see.
But something like that, some need just a
simple screen. Not really too much going
on. Again, you can check that out. Why you
are checking out these platforms,
definitely read, you know, the fees, the
terms and really see if this is one for
you or you need to check out other places,
right? Because, you know, just want to
keep making all these accounts, you know,
having different places you want to build
one that you can build longevity, history
and long term with, right? So other
brokers, Coinbase is another one, but
that's again, crypto. So the top from
highest one, Fidelity, stocks, focus, all
the way down to Coinbase, which shifts to
the crypto blockchain focus. So you have a
wide range right here to select from. If
you need any questions, help, you know,
signing up, definitely reach out. But
these is my top six brokerage accounts
that you can sign up today and start
investing and building up your portfolio.
First and foremost, thank you guys for
keep watching. If you made it to this
part, you know, thank you. You know, don't
forget to hit that like, hit that like
button, hit that subscribe button. So we
get 10,000 subs. All right. I just want
you to know this video that I'm creating
is pretty much just an education
walkthrough for the newbies, for the ones
that are just now getting into it. And for
those that need a refresher, right? The
cycle didn't move in cycles. The market
moving cycles, they move in times, frames,
and you have to know these time frames,
you have to be prepared and ready with the
right tools to see what.